(Amy:)Doesn't matter. You're out. He's in.
(Amy:)No date to the prom,
two dates to a wedding.
(Amy:)Hmm, how times change.
Ha, ha, you have to go to a wedding.
(Howard(off):)I'll get it.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Could you get it?
I said I'm getting it!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Fine, I'll get it.
I got it!
(Howard:)Oh, hi.
(Sheldon:)Hey.
I don't wanna fight.
(Bernadette:)I was just surprised when you sprung
the living-with-your-mom stuff on me.
(Howard:)Yeah, well,
I'm sorry I didn't run it by you first.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)I don't know
who you're talking to, but in or out!
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)We don't need bugs!
(Howard:)The bugs only come here...
(Howard:)...because you're their queen!
Listen, how about this?
Before we make any decision
about where we live, we have a trial run.